This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Lucky D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is stylish!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will come a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
After being separated from his crew,
Luffy set out to rescue his captured brother, Ace.
To do so, he snuck into the government prison, impelled down.
Consider this your punishment, child.
There's no way to neutralize the amount of poison your body has absorbed.
What do you think you're doing to my friend, Bon?
Leave him?
After fighting off the army wolves, Luffy and Bon Clay lost consciousness
and were carried away by the mysterious Inazuma.
When Bon awoke, he found himself in a most queer place.
I bid you welcome.
To impel down level 5.5, bitches!
A secret garden for all y'all prisoners!
This is newcomer land!
Yee-haw!
Luffy's treatment begins!
Eva's miraculous power!
Wow!
Worth it!
Look at that!
No!
Left side, back side!
Wow!
Front side, back side!
Wild side all night!
Wow!
Oh!
I'm dying!
Left side, back side!
Wow!
Oh!
Wow.
Move it, sister!
I said, hee-haw!
Hee-haw!
It's here!
I guess I got a little too excited dancing and cutting loose.
I'm getting dizzy.
Eva, are you all right?
I think I'm gonna collapse now.
Then again, maybe I won't.
You were joking.
You sure fooled me.
I missed a mistake.
You're Eva the miracle worker, aren't you?
Oh, goodness me.
So you've heard about little old war, have you?
Hey, watch your mouth.
Show some respect when you're talking to Eva.
He's royalty, pal.
You gotta bow down before the Queen of Newcoma.
Hail, King Eva!
Hush now, my little candies.
I appreciate the admiration, but don't sweat the small stuff.
I'm not worried about silly things like labels.
People can call me whatever they like.
They can even call me Dookie.
Never call me Dookie!
Why did you say it?
You've got me there.
Is this really Eva, the miracle worker?
The same one that I've worshipped from afar for oh so many years?
Never call me Dookie!
Ha ha!
Emporio Ivankov!
I've been looking for you.
You were the Queen of Kamabaka Kingdom, weren't you?
About 15 years ago, my father, who was the king of my homeland, visited that country of yours and then he...
He came back to us as a queen!
Ah!
Do you have any idea how ashamed I was?
His family and his country were ruined!
I fell for my princely status to nothing but a lonely pirate!
But all the days I spent suffering in this living hell are worth it if I get one shot at the monster who destroyed my life!
No, please!
Don't do it!
Where did you even get that thing?
Oh no!
Don't point that at me!
Have mercy!
I'm fragile!
If you shoot me with that, I'll die!
You'll kill me!
You can't kill me!
You're such a character!
Oh my god, eggs!
Yeah!
Nuh-uh-uh!
Deathwing!
Yeah!
Huh?
Nuh-uh-uh!
Deathwing!
Uh?
Oh!
Hell yeah! That's how we've a pet's an eye, girl! How about some Death Wink?
Yay!
With just a wink, he was able to turn back that bullet!
Emporial Female Hormones!
What was that?
Oh no! What did you chew to me?
You're throwing a fit because your father wanted to become a woman?
Tell me, what's wrong with that?
No! No! No! Stop this! He wouldn't dare!
Two mothers and one son, two fathers and one daughter.
What's wrong with that? You're all family!
Anything but this!
Please, no!
What?!
Wow!
Oh, really?
You have a second!
Fantastic!
Oh, really?
Good gal!
Hi-hah!
You could become a woman, or become a man.
Hee-haw!
Or maybe you could be both!
You should be able to decide for yourself, right?
Hee-haw!
That what you call gender is a label. It's nothing but a border.
I have no need for it, no. Everyone here is beyond it.
Hee-haw! We've all crossed over that silly border.
Which means you're looking at the new human race.
Newcomer!
This is the garden of freedom! Newcomer land!
Hee-haw!
He the rules! He the rules! He the rules! He the rules!
He turned that guy into a woman!
This is the real deal. He truly is a miracle worker.
I bid you welcome! Perhaps you'd like to join in on the fun now!
Hee-haw!
This is so humiliating!
Hee-haw! The poor thing's embarrassed.
She's got a long way to go before becoming a proper citizen of Newcomer!
Huh?
What is it, Bon Boy?
It's an honour to meet you, Eva! I never stopped believing you were still alive!
I'm so glad I found you! You have no idea! If you would hear it, I have a favour to ask of you!
A favour?
My dear friend was poisoned by Magellan! Can you please save his life?
No antidote can help him! He's lying there, dying, and there's nothing I can do!
Please, I'm begging you! I'll give you my life!
I assume you're talking about Straw Hat Boy?
Oof!
Bon Boy!
Hmm?
Did you ever stop to wonder why we treated your injuries in the first place?
To be quite honest, I didn't notice!
We're all just prisoners down here.
We don't have the means to simply take in and care for anyone that we happen to find injured.
We're not nearly so kind.
Hmm.
You see, I took you in and treated you because your friend begged me to do it.
Straw Boy did what?
What?
We've been watching you boys on the monitor, and I gotta say, I'm impressed.
I can't tell if you're lucky or just plain crazy.
Either way, congratulations on making it this far.
For all the good it does you.
Bon.
He was trying to help me and got bitten by those wolves.
Please take care of him.
He's my friend.
I can't let him die.
That's not something just anyone would say.
Not when they're on the verge of death.
Oh.
I didn't know the flower of friendship could bloom in the hell hole like this.
But I do know that if I didn't help him, I'd be no better than a demon in human guise.
Straw Boy.
Anyhow, I already started treatment on your buddy Straw Boy about ten hours ago.
You did?
Aaaaaaah!
Aaaaaah!
Aaaaaaaah!
Aaaaaaah!
But it's gonna be rough.
I need to know that if I help him, I should help him.
I need to help him in the house.
You know that maybe our friendship could bloom in the hell hole like this.
But it's gonna be rough.
I bet the kids out there are wondering what these things are!
Then what's your cold old-fashioned bamboo stills?
You gotta try them sometime, they're fun!
Actually, I made these with wax, so technically they should be called old-fashioned wax stills.
They may be new-fashioned wax stills.
How much longer can these beasts keep this up?
Dawn, now shoo, shoo!
Like that's gonna stop them.
We gotta get off this floor or we're never gonna lose these things.
Just keep running! Move! Move!
Where's the exit? Somebody? Anybody?
Like that, it'sav stop!
Hmm.
Fuck.
Oh...
That sounds awful! What's going on in there?
You call this healing?
He's been screaming like this the entire duration of his treatment,
but I assure you that's part of the process.
We've locked him away for safety.
This'll last another two days.
Huh?
Ten years of your life.
That's what it's going to cost you if I administer this treatment.
It's a high price, but that poison is serious, straw hat boy.
Fine by me.
Just so we're clear, this is a high-risk treatment,
and there's no guarantee that it'll save your life.
In your current condition, you have absolutely no chance of survival.
The best I could do for you through this process
is increase that chance to two or three percent.
What you face right now is a battle the likes of which you have never fought before.
You must temper that will of yours to emerge victorious.
If the poison wins, you will most assuredly die.
But if your spirit wins, you walk away!
It's as simple as that!
All right, then, I wish you a pleasant journey.
To the valley of death, that is!
Emporial Healing Hormone!
No!
Oh, are you pulling my tail?
Strawboy has been wailing in agony like that for ten hours!
Spirit and hormones, these are the vital forces of the human body.
Combined, the two bring forth a tremendous healing potential.
I have drawn out his latent immunity and changed his body to enable him to battle with the deadly poison.
Only time will tell which of the two of them is stronger.
Within that battlefield of a body lies destruction and recovery raging away at extraordinary speeds.
He will survive only if he could withstand all that pain.
And escaping from death does not come cheap.
You can take a look inside if you really want to.
Is there a window?
Strawboy?
How awful! He's gonna die!
It's gonna tear him apart!
His body will be destroyed from the inside out!
That wasn't even him in there! It was a living corpse!
I'm begging you here! Don't let him suffer like that! You have to do something!
Please! Unlock those chains! Stop the bleeding and find a real way to cure him!
Oh, you're the miracle worker, aren't you?
I know he's a mess, but anything is better than this!
Shut the hell up!
I'm helping him the only way I can!
Don't underestimate the human will to live!
The what?
Do you have any idea what it takes to strive against one's own mortality?
To face the ultimate odds?
I'm not a god or an angel or anything like that!
A miracle worker?
You can call me whatever the hell you want, but the truth of the matter is this.
I could never save a fool who doesn't have the will to save himself!
I saved an impoverished country, and a country that was left in ruin after defeat and war!
But in both cases, all I did was draw out their own spirit to live!
That can only happen to people who have the courage to keep on fighting!
Making miracles is never easy!
Easy!
Ace...
とりあえず
That...
じõぃ
とりあえず
えっ
えerd
そっかー
َ
教者
教nt
教徒
テ fre
I'll see you next time.
The end of the pack!